{
    "subject": "resource/Itbox",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "itbox is a networked gambling games terminal which is found in thousands of pubs, leisure centres and amusement arcades in the United Kingdom. Classified as a \"skill with prizes\" (SWP) machine, each itbox terminal typically includes 25 different games. Each game costs 50p or \u00a31 to play and lasts between 10 seconds and several minutes. From most of these games it is possible to win modest cash prizes. Although strictly the name 'itbox' refers only to Leisure Link-made terminals, the name is often casually applied as a genericized trademark to other SWP terminals such as Paragon SWP, Gamesnet, ind:e and Fatbox.",
    "human_readable": "Itbox is a networked gambling games terminal which is found in thousands of pubs, leisure centers and amusement arcades in the United Kingdom.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9374627470970154,
            "question": "Is Itbox a popular gambling terminal in the UK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6019846796989441,
            "question": "What is the primary purpose of an Itbox terminal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5992687940597534,
            "question": "What type of establishment commonly houses Itbox terminals?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5800778269767761,
            "question": "Where is Itbox primarily found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5508623719215393,
            "question": "What does 'networked' mean in the context of Itbox?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5204118490219116,
            "question": "Name some locations where you might find an Itbox."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45045900344848633,
            "question": "What kind of games does Itbox offer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34493640065193176,
            "question": "Is Itbox a recent invention or has it been around for a while?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34479644894599915,
            "question": "What can you infer about the popularity of gambling based on the prevalence of Itbox?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16544751822948456,
            "question": "Who is the target audience for Itbox?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Itbox is a networked gambling games terminal which is found in thousands of pubs, leisure centers and amusement arcades in the United Kingdom.",
            "html": "dbpedia_720_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you infer about the popularity of gambling based on the prevalence of Itbox?",
            "html": "dbpedia_720_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Itbox a recent invention or has it been around for a while?",
            "html": "dbpedia_720_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of games does Itbox offer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_720_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_720_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_720_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_720_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_720_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_720_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_720_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_720_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_720_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_720_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_720_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text explicitly states: \"itbox is a networked gambling games terminal which is found in thousands of pubs, leisure centres and amusement arcades in the United Kingdom.\"  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe information provided supports the triple that Itbox is a networked gambling games terminal which is found in thousands of pubs, leisure centers and amusement arcades in the United Kingdom. The documents mention that itbox terminals are typically installed in pubs, leisure centres and amusement arcades in the UK, and provide further details about their features and functionality. Therefore, the value for the \"output\" key is \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context information supports the statement that \"Itbox is a networked gambling games terminal which is found in thousands of pubs, leisure centres and amusement arcades in the United Kingdom.\" This information can be directly derived from the text present in `25.txt`."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}